The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
A real savage
with Nascent Soul cultivation !
Go,
kill them all !
Die !
How is that possible ?!
This is...
It's...
a real savage.
You seem to know about the savage's ranks.
I'd appreciate it if you could
tell me what you know.
These savages
are known as the Forsaken Immortal Clan.
They are split into two types:
Shamans
and Warriors.
Their power comes from
the tattoos on their bodies.
This method is what allows them
to use spells and raise their cultivation.
The greater the number of leaves,
the stronger they are.
So this is how the Forsaken Immortal Clan cultivates.
It's very different from us.
A 5-leaf Shaman...
Soul Formation !
Forsaken Immortal Clan\N5-leaf Shaman
They can feed on the tattoos to enhance their cultivation.
This cultivation method
is unheard of.
It's really weird.
Split up !
Go towards the north,
we will meet at the third floor entrance.
Yes !
Second floor of the\NImmortal Graveyard
If you want to fight,
I'll accept the duel.
I'd like to learn how you did
to absorb your comrade.
There's no spiritual energy in his body.
But the tattoos
contain a mysterious power.
Mo Mo\NForsaken Immortal Clan\N5-leaf Shaman
Invaders of this planet,
you guys broke the agreement !
100 years haven’t passed yet,
so anyone who enters will
die !
This savage's tattoo power
is really overbearing.
Chop !
You will eat Grandpa Xu's sword !
Restriction wall !
Each time I use it
I need to consume a top quality spirit stone.
The price is too high...
You were presumptuous
so Grandpa Xu chopped you !
Their cultivation method
cannot be underestimated.
6-leaf...
Ka Mo\NForsaken Immortal Clan\N6-leaf Shaman
Master...
Get ready
Okay.
Tai Zhou\NKa Mo's disciple\NForsaken Immortal Clan
This beast
will die !
Looks like it turned out well.
This is savage's language...
Who are you ?
If you leave now
and don't disturb my cultivation again
I won't pursue today's matter.
When I entered the cultivation world
I met a weirdo named Adai.
Was he related to the Forsaken Immortal Clan ?
Invader,
it's time for you to show yourself.
Hello,
I'm Ka Mo of the Forsaken Immortal Clan,
6-leaf Shaman.
I'm Wang Lin,
Soul Formation cultivator.
It is not yet time for the 100 year agreement.
Every cultivators who trespasses
must die.
Since you let my disciple absorb the beast blood,
I won’t make it hard on you.
He used the blood from the beast
to make tattoos just now.
Is that a secret technique of your Forsaken Immortal Clan ?
My Forsaken Immortal Clan uses tattoos
to absorb the powers from these beasts.
The stronger the beast,
the more power we gain.
If this technique
is so domineering,
why does your clan
live in this barren underground ?
Planet Suzaku
was originally our home.
Back then,
when the country of Suzaku reached rank 6
this planet was given to them by the Cultivation Alliance.
To obtain this planet,
they fought a war.
The Forsaken Immortal Clan lost 90% of their people.
The few survivors
hid in the Immortal Graveyard
and cannot leave it anymore.
Do not enter the third floor.
In the third floor,
there is a 7-leaf shaman from my tribe,
the equivalent to a Soul Transformation cultivator.
If you leave now,
there is still a chance for you to live.
Thanks for the heads up.
Master,
why didn't you capture him
and turn him in to the chief ?
If I'm not mistaken
the tattoo soul behind him
belongs to Mo Mo.
Someone who can kill a 5-leaf shaman
without getting hurt
is not someone I have confidence in capturing.
Also,
you would be in danger.
Far North of the\Nsecond floor of the Immortal Graveyard
Turtle beast
If it weren't for saving us,
he wouldn't have been hurt.
It's just that we have limited talent,
that's why we're dragging Master down.
Master Sun has suffered a great misfortune.
No one has heard from Brother Wang.
Only these two idiots are left...
If we meet a tough opponent again...
You're stupid,
but you know how to protect your master.
Brother Wang !
What's the matter ?
Master Sun led us all the way
to the entrance.
But we met a shaman that used a strange technique
to injure Master Sun
and make his mind unclear.
Kneel !
Master !
What's going on here ?
Trap !
Fellow cultivator Sun, still not sober yet ?!
The savage
broke through to 6-leaf before he died
and tried to turn me into a puppet.
This technique is very tyrannical,
I can't calm down to disperse the curse.
Brother Wang...
Help me !
Senior, don't act hastily.
Master !
Only a life or death crisis
could have broken this curse.
This man's reputation isn't baseless.
Brother Wang,
thank you.
Master !
Thank you again Brother Wang.
No problem.
This is a very dangerous place.
Still no signs
of the Zhi Xin duo.
All I know is that the Reincarnation Tree is on the west of the third floor.
Why don't we go first
and wait for them there.
To tell you the truth,
my two disciples have more than 100 years of lifespan.
They will each sacrifice 60 years
to make the Reincarnation Fruits grow.
That's why they're here.
each one of us
will take one fruit.
Brother Wang,
help me out.
I’m willing to give you artifacts in exchange !
Ancient Bell
I obtained this object inside the belly of a beast.
My cultivation is limited so I cannot see through it.
It should be an ancient artifact.
It's for you Brother Wang.
I hope you can take me with you
to give me a chance
to cultivate under the Reincarnation Tree.
Third floor of the\NImmortal Graveyard
Za Gu\NForsaken Immortal Clan\N6-leaf Shaman
Injured but not dead ?
A 6-leaf Shaman !
A Turtle beast !
Di Ya\NForsaken Immortal Clan\N6-leaf Shaman
Fellow cultivator Sun,
they aren't interested in you.
They just want your Spirit Beast's blood to make tattoos.
This beast has been with Master for 100 years...
If we fight to the death, we may be able to save it.
In a emergency, one must be decisive.
I had no choice but to do it.
Brother Wang,
it's there !
Reincarnation Tree
Cultivation is a heaven defying act.
Since he had the fate to arrive here,
we should not interfere.
We'll do the rest.
I'd like to ask the Master and Senior
to protect us.
How many fruits do you think will grow ?
At least
2 Reincarnation Fruits.
One for you and one for me.
If there are 3,
I'll take the extra one.
After all, it's my disciples that are sacrificing their lifespan.
I hope Brother Wang understands.
That's fine.
But the branches of this Reincarnation Tree
belong to me.
3 Reincarnation Fruits !
Kill them all.
Damn it !
How much longer ?
3 hours
Fantastic !
Attack together !
What's this ?!
Get out of the way !
Explode !
These are just 4 or 5-leaf Shamans.
If there are two or more 6-leaf Shamans,
then there's nothing I can do.
Besides, on this floor
there is a Shaman equivalent to Soul Transformation,
a 7-leaf Shaman.
It's too slow.
Mast...
Master !
You were good disciples, consider it your reward.
Sacrificing their entire lifespan
to accelerate the growth of the Reincarnation Fruits...
Reincarnation Fruits
This Sun guy
is really ruthless.
This is it !
Attack !
Restriction Spears !
Chi Mu\NForsaken Immortal Clan\N6-leaf Warrior
A Warrior...
To let go of the consequences of my actions
is to ignore the law of cause and effect
like scattered ink.
As destiny falls
in exchange for this moment of tainted dreams.
It makes the mountains lose their colors,
wither and melt into rivers.
Who can deceive
the law of the heavens ?
Countless generations
have tried before me.
But how could I not catch my dreams
within my warm fingers ?
You're at my side when I'm alone
giving me the strength to fight the will of the heavens.
Fortunately, my mind was open and honest.
I'm sorry we never got to see the fireworks
in the streets.
Can I break the vortex of our destiny ?
Can I break the rules ?
To run towards you !
I will fight the law of the heavens and the law of cause and effect
to cut down this tribulation with my own hands
and break through the reincarnation cycle.
All of that for the stars in your eyes.
I wish to bend this dream for the fire in my heart.
If your soul is willing to wander,
can I still take your hands
and hold them tight ?
I will defy the heavens and prevent the stars from falling.
I will overthrow the Immortals and the Demons in my heart.
I dream of destroying
the shackles of our fate.
You're the only one that can ignore the law of cause and effect.
You're the hardest to let go of.
I want to be with you again
so I can look in your eyes.
Even for a moment, it's worth it.